Yuttapichai Paul Linglom

Junior Software Developer

Address: Bangbuathong, Nonthaburi 11110

Telephone : +66 6 5553 2616 **Email** : linglomst@gmail.com

Github : https://github.com/TreenethLin
Linkedin : Yuttapichai Paul Linglom | LinkedIn

Personal Interests

- Web Development
- Data Analytics
- Machine Learning
- Digital Marketing
- Business
 Administration

Personal Statement

"Originally from the south of Thailand (Suratthani), I am an ex-beachboy who fall in love with problem-solving and always believes that anyone can be better if they do not stop learning"

Highly Motivated, Innovative and task-driven professional with 3+ years of experience in human resources and recruiting across diverse industries. Excited to be a career switcher, starting a new challenge in my career as a junior software developer. I want a highly rewarding career where I can use my skills and knowledge for organizational and personal growth.

TECHNICAL & PROGRAMMING SKILLS

· Git · Bash · JavaScript · HTML & CSS · React.js · Node.js · Figma · Canva



















Personality & Soft Skills

- I am an introvert person (INTJ)
- Good communication in English (TOEIC SCORE: 785)
- · Team communication and active listening skills
- Leadership skills
- · Problem-solving skills
- Optimistic, enthusiastic and hardworking
- Fast learner and multitasking skills
- Strong management and negotiation in terms of customer acquisition and business achievement.
- Lifelong learner

WORK EXPERIENCE

Recruitment Team Leader Decathlon Bangyai (Nonthaburi, Thailand), June 2020 – June 2021



- Responsible for the full recruitment cycle for Decathlon Bangyai Store, starting from Job description development, HR marketing, candidate sourcing, interviewing
- · Work closely with store leader to achieve the recruitment goal
- Managing and training (take care of 3 team members)
- Carry out all other related tasks.

Recruitment Consultant (Middle to Executive Search) JAC International (Bangkok, Thailand), Jan 2020 - June 2020



- Handle a full recruitment cycle from understanding clients' requirements, candidate sourcing, and candidate coaching until onboarding (including negotiating sessions).
- Screening resumes, interviewing candidates, writing resume summary before profiling the suitable candidates for client's considerations.
- Be responsible to achieve an individual's sales targets.
- To participate in networking/marketing events from time to time.

Host & Walking Tour Guide Once Again Hostel (Bangkok, Thailand), Jul 2018 – Jun 2020



- Work at the front desk, serving visitors by greeting, welcoming, and directing them appropriately.
- Manage daily tasks in hostel including check-in and check-out and inventory control
- · Launch special events and bring the guests to join every week
- Enforce rules and policies of the hotel
- · Create daily activity reports or other reports requested by management

Junior Recruiter Aston Smartphone (Nonthaburi, Thailand), May 2016 – Sep 2017



- Identifying future hiring needs and developing job descriptions and specifications.
- · Attracting suitable candidates through databases, online employment forums, social media, etc.
- Conducting interviews and sorting through applicants to fill open positions.
- Assessing applicants' knowledge, skills, and experience to best suit open positions.
- Promoting the company's reputation and attractiveness as a good employment opportunity.
- Managing internship programs.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS



Bachelor's Degree, 2012 - 2016

Thammasat University,
Faculty of Political Science



Full-Time Bootcamp, 2022

Generation Thailand
Junior Software Development Program

TRAINING

- Create a Front-End App with React (Codecademy)
- Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate
- SQL for Data Science (University of California Davis: Coursera)
- R Programming Track (Datacamp)

ACTIVITIES AND AWARDS

- King Bhumibol Adulyadej Award (1st Place Direct Entrance Examination)
- Spokesperson, Thammasat University Student Council 2013
- Member of Thammasat University Debate Team (1st Runner Up Prince Maha Chakri Sirindhorn Cup)
- Independent singer and songwriter

REFERENCE PERSON